I'm wearing my latex catsuit by Visage with the fake boobs and I do have a
discount code but today's video is all about combining this catsuit with some
fashion pieces to create new looks. If you know my channel you may have seen
these pieces already they're by Restrict and I'm going to put them on top of the
catsuit now. Okay I put everything on I haven't seen myself yet so I'm going to
check them out
I love the look with the boots and the tie straps and everything.
I have to admit I think the boobs are too big for the corset. So I think I would
try to
wear it without the corset.
I thought it would look better with the corset but I think because the leather is so stiff
and the boobs are so big it kind of stretches it in a wrong way.
So for example it's not really tight here so I'm going to get rid of it.
all right I have to say it looks way better let me just adjust the panty straps here
it looks really fetishy without the corset though so that's definitely a look you have to be
confident in. Otherwise I love the combination of red, black and gold. In this case, the
straps are sliding a bit down since the latex is slippery, of course. Yeah, nice. I think
it's a great look. Maybe I would add a black corset next time I wear it in this combination.
The thing is about the neck corset, it's definitely restricting my movement, but you can turn
I hope what you're up to see the mirror is a bit hard actually I like the back view definitely
nice remember my video how to get your girlfriend into latex I was talking about persuading your
partner person to wear latex and making this video kind of reminds me about that well and
first step of that would actually be how to get a girlfriend and I'm really happy to tell you that
I partnered up with the wing girl method as a sponsor for today's video founded
by renowned dating expert and fellow youtuber Marnie your personal wing girl
whose channel has grown over 1.4 million subscribers as well as being featured on
MTV dr. drew ask men and penthouse her goal is to help improve the dating lives
of men because let's be honest some guys just suck at flirting and that's where
Marnie comes in she has helped thousands of men transform their dating lives with
her science-based flirting method the F-formula which has been used by a lot
of men worldwide. This proven system helps you attract the woman you want and
build your confidence. This isn't for guys who are content with being alone
forever. It's for those ready to break free from their flirting failures and
finally date the women they deserve. If you're not taking action now you're just
setting yourself up to be left behind while others grip the opportunities
you're too scared to go after. And even if you think a girl is out of your league or not interested,
this step-by-step formula can change that. It shows you exactly how to make any woman eager
to escalate with you, date you, sleep with you and be with you. No need to look like a model or have
millions in your bank account. With the F-formula, those things aren't necessary. Apply this method
and you'll start seeing results almost immediately. Why trust Marnie's F-formula? Over 100,000 men
have already experienced life-changing results. This is your chance to date like
the top 10% of men. And because the Wingirl method is sponsoring today's
video they're offering my viewers an unbeatable deal. Just click the first
link in the description now, grab your exclusive preview of the F-formula
completely for free. Plus if you decide to pick up the full program you'll get
an extra 50% off. So if you're tired of failing at flirting and being stuck on
the sidelines stop wasting time take control of your dating life click the link below and get
access right now all right i changed into the next outfit and i paired my eastern brood datex skirt
with my new necklace by 666999 and of course a metal belt so we see the catsuit of course as a
top but also basically as tights and I love this look I think it turned out
really really great I am so in love with this necklace I'm so happy I bought it
at German Fittish Mall so this latex is latex on the outside and fabric on the
inside we have a spandex fabric on the inside it actually did slide really well
on the latex so it was really easy to get into the skirt I was surprised and
And also there's a zipper in the back here which also helped.
But yeah, I think this is a very, very elegant look.
I'm surprised myself how much I like it.
I don't think it looks too fetishy like with the red accessories before.
This is more classy.
Datex is stretchy but the skirt is cuffed really tight.
So it's more like a bit of a hobbled skirt.
I can't I can walk around but there's not a lot of range of motion
it's really helpful to have help from someone putting on the shoes
for the final outfit I have these pants I'm going to attempt to put them over the catsuit
legs let's see how that goes I'm going to change okay I put my jeans on as you can see it's still
catsuit underneath and of course this could already act as the outfit with the catsuit being
simply the top but I wanted to increase the layering throughout the video so I'm going to put
the jacket on as well. So I'm going for basically a four-letter look with the coated jeans and this
fabric jacket. I've actually worn this two business trips. And now the latex is very
subtle. I learned not to pronounce the B and basically hidden but I think it's a
great look. I definitely like it. I decided to add a belt because I thought
there are some accessories missing still debating where or not to put on a choker
but we have the tiny business belt which is also shiny so I hope this will be a
match actually not sure because I think it's too tiny maybe what do you think
and this is the look with the clothes jacket I actually can't really close it all the way
because of the fake boobs if you want to know more about these fake boobies then check out the
video about the cat suit I did and this is the full look I paired my buffaloes with the outfit
because they're comfy they're cool and they look badass I love them why did I buy them so late in
my life anyway yeah that's the look tell me in the comments which look you like best don't forget
to check out all the links in the description text also the f-formula link I mentioned earlier
and the link to the catsuit video if you're interested in that I hope you enjoyed this
video and did enjoy the looks I created I definitely did so yeah see you in the next
video have a nice day bye oh and p.s this is also a look I love to do with a latex catsuit
just put a t-shirt on the top of it and the belt I usually use band t-shirts
because I own a lot of them and I think this looks very casual very comfy very cool